A Guide to the Policy Office Legislative Files of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
- Special Session I: 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly, Chapter 1 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Special Session I: 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly, Chapter 2 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- SB 187 (99) Jury Selection (Box 12, Folder 1)
- SB 220 (99) VRS; Long-Term Care Insurance Program (Box 12, Folder 2)
- SB 244 (99) Accident and Sickness Insurance; Coverage for Diabetes (Box 12, Folder 3)
- SB 325 (99) Driver's Licenses; Suspension (Box 12, Folder 4)
- SB 370 (99) Exclusion of Victims of Crime (Box 4, Folder 5)
- SB 430 (99) Health Insurance; Mental Health Coverage (Box 12, Folder 6)
- SB 444 (99) Felony Fees (Box 12, Folder 7)
- SB 448 (99) Liability Insurance; Motor Vehicles, Aircraft and Watercraft (Box 12, Folder 8)
- SB 559 (99) Verification of Citizenship of Certain Students (Box 12, Folder 9)
- SB 582 (99) Wetlands Mitigation Banks (Box 12, Folder 10)
- SB 720 (99) Special License Plates; Honorably Discharged Members of Armed Services (Box 12, Folder 11)
- SB 721 (99) Dangerous Dogs (Box 12, Folder 12)
- SB 724 (99) Annexation Moratorium; Aid for Localities (Box 12, Folder 13)
- SB 726 (99) Shenandoah Town Center (Box 12, Folder 14)
- SB 728 (99) Department of Personnel and Training; State Health Insurance Plan (Box 12, Folder 15)
- SB 729 (99) J. Kenneth Robinson Parkway (Box 12, Folder 16)
- SB 730 (99) Courts of Record; Indexing by Tax Map Reference (Box 12, Folder 17)
- SB 732 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Meals on Wheels of Greater Richmond, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 18)
- SB 734 (99) Highway Projects; Utility Relocation Costs (Box 12, Folder 19)
- SB 735 (99) Sales Tax on Food Products for Home Consumption (Box 12, Folder 20)
- SB 736 (99) Property Exchange in Pedlar Hills Natural Area (Box 12, Folder 21)
- SB 738 (99) Local Regulation of Sidewalks (Box 12, Folder 22)
- SB 739 (99) Virginia Water and Waste Authorities Act (Box 12, Folder 23)
- SB 740 (99) Amber Warning Lights (Box 12, Folder 24)
- SB 741 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Capital Area Community Food Bank, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 25)
- SB 744 (99) Nurse Practitioners' Prescriptive Authority; Supervisory Ratios (Box 12, Folder 26)
- SB 745 (99) Bluefield Town Charter (Box 12, Folder 27)
- SB 746 (99) Clyde Bowling Bridge (Box 12, Folder 28)
- SB 749 (99) Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) (Box 12, Folder 29)
- SB 754 (99) Laser Speed "Guns" (Box 12, Folder 30)
- SB 755 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Somerset-Old Creek Recreation Club, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 31)
- SB 756 (99) Falls Church City Charter (Box 12, Folder 32)
- SB 757 (99) County Manager in Arlington County (Box 12, Folder 33)
- SB 760 (99) Sex Offender Register (Box 12, Folder 34)
- SB 764 (99) Laser Speed "Guns" (Box 12, Folder 35)
- SB 765 (99) Roanoke Higher Education Authority; Membership (Box 12, Folder 36)
- SB 767 (99) Public Assistance; Initiative for Employment Not Welfare (VIEW) (Box 12, Folder 37)
- SB 772 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Vetshouse, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 38)
- SB 773 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Judeo-Christian Outreach Center, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 39)
- SB 774 (99) Sales and Use Tax; Transfer of Manufacturer's Tooling (Box 12, Folder 40)
- SB 775 (99) "Photo-Red" Enforcement of Traffic Light Signals (Box 12, Folder 41)
- SB 776 (99) Real Estate Tax Assessments; New Construction (Box 12, Folder 42)
- SB 777 (99) Bristol City Charter (Box 12, Folder 43)
- SB 778 (99) Combined Transient Occupancy and Food and Beverage Tax (Box 12, Folder 44)
- SB 779 (99) Literary Fund Loans; Legal Opinion Required (Box 12, Folder 45)
- SB 780 (99) Local Business Taxes; Appeals and Rulings (Box 12, Folder 46)
- SB 781 (99) Sales and Use Tax Liability of Industrial Development Authorities (Box 12, Folder 47)
- SB 782 (99) Medical-Related Sale and Use Tax Exemption (Box 12, Folder 48)
- SB 783 (99) Property Tax Exemption; American Type Culture Collection (Box 12, Folder 49)
- SB 784 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Forest Youth Athletic Association (Box 12, Folder 50)
- SB 785 (99) Property Tax Exemption; The Maupin-Sizemore Foundation (Box 12, Folder 51)
- SB 786 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Point of Honor, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 52)
- SB 788 (99) Smithfield Town Center (Box 12, Folder 53)
- SB 789 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Virginia Association for the Blind, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 54)
- SB 790 (99) Sales Tax from Suffolk Conference Center (Box 12, Folder 55)
- SB 794 (99) Reproductions of Tax Documents (Box 12, Folder 56)
- SB 795 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Newport News Green Foundation, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 57)
- SB 799 (99) Speed Limits on Route 288 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- SB 801 (99) Care of Confederate Graves (Box 12, Folder 59)
- SB 805 (99) Emergency Services (Box 12, Folder 60)
- SB 806 (99) Virginia Freedom of Information Act (Box 12, Folder 61)
- SB 808 (99) Secretary of Technology created (Box 12, Folder 62)
- SB 810 (99) VRS Early Retirement Options for Teachers (Box 12, Folder 63)
- SB 811 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Beach Health Clinic, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 64)
- SB 814 (99) Covington Town Charter (Box 12, Folder 65)
- SB 815 (99) Felony Homicide (Box 12, Folder 66)
- SB 816 (99) Sickness and Disability Program for State Employees (Box 12, Folder 67)
- SB 817 (99) Elementary School Character Education Programs (Box 12, Folder 68)
- SB 818 (99) VRS Early Retirement Options (Box 12, Folder 69)
- SB 819 (99) Definitions of Certain Words in the Code of Virginia (Box 12, Folder 70)
- SB 820 (99) Criminal Procedure; Bail (Box 12, Folder 71)
- SB 821 (99) Supplemental Salary of the Clerk of Circuit Court (Box 12, Folder 72)
- SB 822 (99) Claims; Robert A. and Victoria R. Slis (Box 12, Folder 73)
- SB 825 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Oliero, Ltd. (Box 12, Folder 74)
- SB 827 (99) School Safety (Box 12, Folder 75)
- SB 829 (99) Sales and Use Exemptions (Box 12, Folder 76)
- SB 830 (99) Uniform Statewide Building Code; Inspection of Elevators (Box 12, Folder 77)
- SB 831 (99) VRS; Employer to Withdraw Funds (Box 12, Folder 78)
- SB 832 (99) Newport News City Charter (Box 12, Folder 79)
- SB 833 (99) Fredericksburg City Charter (Box 12, Folder 80)
- SB 835 (99) Crimes; Bodily Injury Cause by Prisoner, Probationer or Parolee (Box 12, Folder 81)
- SB 837 (99) Additional Transient Occupancy Tax; Sunset Date (Box 12, Folder 82)
- SB 838 (99) Obstruction of Justice (Box 12, Folder 83)
- SB 840 (99) Property Tax Exemption; CANDII (Box 12, Folder 84)
- SB 841 (99) DUI; Additional Alternative Sanctions for Habitual Offenders (Box 12, Folder 85)
- SB 843 (99) Benefits of State Employees Transferred to Local Health Departments (Box 12, Folder 86)
- SB 845 (99) Civil Commitment of Sexually Violent Predators (Box 12, Folder 87)
- SB 846 (99) Chesapeake City Charter (Box 12, Folder 88)
- SB 847 (99) Sales Tax Refund on Building Materials (Box 12, Folder 89)
- SB 848 (99) Assault and Battery Against a Family or Household Member (Box 12, Folder 90)
- SB 849 (99) Money Laundering Act; Seizure and Business License Forfeiture (Box 12, Folder 91)
- SB 851 (99) Cruelty to Animals (Box 12, Folder 92)
- SB 853 (99) Violent Felony Offenses (Box 12, Folder 93)
- SB 857 (99) Four for Life (Box 12, Folder 94)
- SB 859 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Larrymore Lawns Community Park Association (Box 12, Folder 95)
- SB 860 (99) Norfolk City Charter (Box 12, Folder 96)
- SB 861 (99) Claims; Estate of Arlene C. Bergers (Box 13, Folder 1)
- SB 862 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Meals on Wheels of Greater Richmond (Box 13, Folder 2)
- SB 864 (99) Agricultural Sales and Use Tax Exemptions; Forest Products (Box 13, Folder 3)
- SB 865 (99) Study; Solid Waste, Changes in Regulations (Box 13, Folder 4)
- SB 868 (99) Interest Rates; Tax Overpayments (Box 13, Folder 5)
- SB 869 (99) Sales and Use Tax; Medical-Related Exemptions (Box 13, Folder 6)
- SB 870 (99) Claims; Beverly Q. Russell (Box 13, Folder 7)
- SB 872 (99) ABC; Definitions (Box 13, Folder 8)
- SB 873 (99) Property Tax Exemption; Goodwin House, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 9)
- SB 874 (99) Sex Offender Registry (Box 13, Folder 10)
- SB 876 (99) VRS Retirement with 30 Years of Service (Box 13, Folder 11)
- SB 877 (99) Income Tax Deduction for Teacher Education Expenses (Box 13, Folder 12)
- SB 879 (99) Car Tax Relief; Reimbursement of Administrative Costs (Box 13, Folder 13)
- SB 881 (99) Virginia Computer Crimes Act; Electronic Mail (Box 13, Folder 14)
- SB 885 (99) Juvenile Delinquents; Gangs (Box 13, Folder 15)
- SB 886 (99) Juvenile Delinquents; Restitution (Box 16)
- SB 887 (99) Crimes; Mob Defined (Box 13, Folder 17)
- SB 888 (99) VRS; Prior Service Credit for Interruption (Box 13, Folder 18)
- SB 889 (99) Care of Public School Students Diagnosed with Type I Diabetes (Box 13, Folder 19)
- SB 892 (99) Insurance Licensees; Requirement to Report; Felony Convictions (Box 13, Folder 20)
- SB 893 (99) Industrial Development and Revenue Bond Act (Box 13, Folder 21)
- SB 894 (99) Health Maintenance Organizations; Annual and Financial Statements (Box 13, Folder 22)
- SB 895 (99) Insurance; Technical Amendments (Box 13, Folder 23)
- SB 896 (99) Regional Juvenile Detention Commissions (Box 13, Folder 24)
- SB 897 (99) Banking and Finance; Investment in Stock or Securities (Box 13, Folder 25)
- SB 899 (99) Public Service Corporations and Electric Authorities; Eminent Domain (Box 13, Folder 26)
- SB 900 (99) Insurance; Consultants and Surplus Lines Brokers (Box 13, Folder 27)
- SB 901 (99) Accident and Sickness Insurance; Establishment of MCHIP (Box 13, Folder 28)
- SB 902 (99) Self Storage Facilities; Liens (Box 13, Folder 29)
- SB 903 (99) Issuance of Process for Arrest of a Person for Capital Murder (Box 13, Folder 30)
- SB 907 (99) Adoption; Custody (Box 13, Folder 31)
- SB 908 (99) State Corporation Commission Taxes; Refund of Overpayment (Box 13, Folder 32)
- SB 909 (99) Medical Malpractice Insurance; Examinations (Box 13, Folder 33)
- SB 910 (99) Virginia Caregivers Grant Program (Box 13, Folder 34)
- SB 911 (99) Impact Statements on Legislation (Box 13, Folder 35)
- SB 912 (99) Public Procurement Act; Exemptions (Box 13, Folder 36)
- SB 914 (99) Correcting Erroneous Real Estate Management (Box 13, Folder 37)
- SB 915 (99) Injury to Property (Box 13, Folder 38)
- SB 917 (99) Criminal Information Network (Box 13, Folder 39)
- SB 918 (99) Dangerous and Vicious Dogs (Box 13, Folder 40)
- SB 919 (99) Savings Trust Accounts; Income Tax Deduction (Box 13, Folder 41)
- SB 921 (99) Driver's licenses; Persons Under 18 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- SB 922 (99) Peeping or Spying (Box 13, Folder 43)
- SB 923 (99) Voluntary Income Tax Contributions; Foundation for Humanities and Public Policy (Box 13, Folder 44)
- SB 924 (99) Driving Under the Influence (Box 13, Folder 45)
- SB 925 (99) Crimes; Contempt (Box 13, Folder 46)
- SB 926 (99) Board of Accountancy (Box 13, Folder 47)
- SB 927 (99) Criminal Sentencing Commission (Box 13, Folder 48)
- SB 930 (99) Interjurisdictional Law-Enforcement Authority (Box 13, Folder 49)
- SB 932 (99) Qualifications of Temporarily Employed Teachers (Box 13, Folder 50)
- SB 933 (99) Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Security Deposits; Interest (Box 13, Folder 51)
- SB 935 (99) Animal Welfare (Box 13, Folder 52)
- SB 937 (99) Local Liability Insurance (Box 13, Folder 53)
- SB 938 (99) Assessments of Real Property in Certain Counties (Box 13, Folder 54)
- SB 939 (99) Laser Speed Determination Devices (Box 13, Folder 55)
- SB 940 (99) Disposition of Land by VDOT (Box 13, Folder 56)
- SB 941 (99) Civil Remedies; Service by Publication (Box 13, Folder 57)
- SB 942 (99) Health, Cancer Registry (Box 13, Folder 58)
- SB 944 (99) Health Professions; Health Practitioners Intervention Program (Box 13, Folder 59)
- SB 947 (99) Crimes; Concealed Weapons (Box 13, Folder 60)
- SB 949 (99) Bounties for Coyotes (Box 13, Folder 61)
- SB 956 (99) I-64 Weighing Station (Box 13, Folder 62)
- SB 957 (99) Historic Rehabilitation Tax Credit (Box 13, Folder 63)
- SB 958 (99) Corporations; Dissenter's Rights (Box 13, Folder 64)
- SB 959 (99) Finance Charges by Sellers of Goods and Services, Inc. (Box 13, Folder 65)
- SB 961 (99) Vehicular Warning Lights (Box 13, Folder 66)
- SB 962 (99) Compulsory School Attendance; GED Testing (Box 13, Folder 67)
- SB 963 (99) Health; Onsite Sewage Evaluations (Box 13, Folder 68)
- SB 964 (99) Good Time Credits Earned in Jail (Box 13, Folder 69)
- SB 966 (99) Juvenile Offenses (Box 13, Folder 70)
- SB 967 (99) Exemptions from Jury Service (Box 13, Folder 71)
- SB 968 (99) Meals Taxes (Box 13, Folder 72)
- SB 971 (99) Commonwealth's Surplus Motor Vehicles; Welfare Reform (Box 13, Folder 73)
- SB 974 (99) Virginia Regional Industrial Facilities Act (Box 13, Folder 74)
- SB 975 (99) Data Reported to the Board of Medicine (Box 13, Folder 75)
- SB 976 (99) Not Guilty by Reason of Insanity (Box 13, Folder 76)
- SB 977 (99) Regulation of Itinerant Merchants (Box 13, Folder 77)
- SB 979 (99) "No Wake" Buoys (Box 13, Folder 77)
- SB 983 (99) Liability in Connection with the Year 2000 Date (Box 13, Folder 79)
- SB 984 (99) Insurance Agents; Bail Bond Agents (Box 13, Folder 80)
- SB 990 (99) Custody and Visitation (Box 13, Folder 81)
- SB 991 (99) Sex Offender Treatment Providers (Box 13, Folder 82)
- SB 992 (99) Antique and Model Boilers (Box 13, Folder 82)
- SB 995 (99) Classification for Business Personal Property (Box 13, Folder 84)
- SB 996 (99) Civil Actions for Felons Sued by Crime Victims (Box 13, Folder 85)
- SB 999 (99) Property Owners' Associations; Amendment of Declaration (Box 13, Folder 86)
- SB 1002 (99) Absentee Ballots for Persons Registered for Federal Elections (Box 13, Folder 87)
- SB 1004 (99) Licensed Social Workers; Continuing Education Requirements (Box 13, Folder 88)
- SB 1008 (99) Overpayments of Local Taxes (Box 13, Folder 89)
- SB 1010 (99) Patient Health Records (Box 13, Folder 90)
- SB 1011 (99) Crime Victims (Box 13, Folder 91)
- SB 1014 (99) Child Custody; Entrustments; Termination of Parental Rights (Box 13, Folder 92)
- SB 1015 (99) Insurance, Regulation of Rates, Exemptions; Large Deducible Plans (Box 13, Folder 93)
- SB 1017 (99) Bank Franchise Tax; Computation of Net Capital (Box 13, Folder 94)
- SB 1018 (99) Virginia Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Act (Box 13, Folder 95)
- SB 1019 (99) Credit Unions; Membership (Box 13, Folder 96)
- SB 1021 (99) Neighborhood Assistance Act (Box 13, Folder 97)
- SB 1023 (99) Freedom of Information (Box 13, Folder 98)
- SB 1026 (99) Freedom of Information Act; Electronic Communication Meetings (Box 13, Folder 99)
- SB 1027 (99) Official Artisan Center of the Commonwealth (Box 14, Folder 1)
- SB 1028 (99) BPOL Tax; License Tax on Motor Vehicle Dealers (Box 14, Folder 2)
- SB 1029 (99) Soil Survey (Box 14, Folder 3)
- SB 1035 (99) Family Violence (Box 14, Folder 4)
- SB 1037 (99) Health; Childhood Immunizations (Box 5)
- SB 1039 (99) Juvenile Competency (Box 14, Folder 6)
- SB 1042 (99) Eligibility for In-State Tuition (Box 14, Folder 7)
- SB 1045 (99) Curb Ramps (Box 14, Folder 8)
- SB 1047 (99) Family Life Education; Abstinence Education (Box 14, Folder 9)
- SB 1049 (99) Virginia Public School Construction Grants Program (Box 14, Folder 10)
- SB 1050 (99) Transient Occupancy Tax (Box 14, Folder 11)
- SB 1053 (99) Annexation Moratorium (Box 14, Folder 12)
- SB 1054 (99) Mental Health; Disclosure of Information (Box 14, Folder 13)
- SB 1055 (99) State Mental Health Facility Directors (Box 14, Folder 14)
- SB 1056 (99) Commission on Intergovernmental Cooperation; Membership (Box 14, Folder 15)
- SB 1057 (99) Board for Contractors; Exemptions from Licensure (Box 14, Folder 16)
- SB 1062 (99) Health; Private Wells (Box 14, Folder 17)
- SB 1063 (99) Outdoor Advertising (Box 14, Folder 18)
- SB 1064 (99) Use Tax Distribution in Certain Localities (Box 14, Folder 19)
- SB 1065 (99) Industrial Development Authorities (Box 14, Folder 20)
- SB 1066 (99) Industrial Development Authorities; Compensation of Directors (Box 14, Folder 21)
- SB 1067 (99) Annual School Board Reports (Box 14, Folder 22)
- SB 1068 (99) HOV Lanes in Tidewater Area (Box 14, Folder 23)
- SB 1069 (99) Assault and Battery Against Household Member (Box 14, Folder 24)
- SB 1071 (99) Money Order Sales; Designation of Payees (Box 14, Folder 25)
- SB 1073 (99) Virginia Racing Commission; Consideration of Applications (Box 14, Folder 26)
- SB 1076 (99) Corporate Income Tax; Apportionment (Box 14, Folder 27)
- SB 1077 (99) Substance Abuse Screening of Certain Offenders (Box 14, Folder 28)
- SB 1084 (99) Custody and Visitation; Best Interests of Child (Box 14, Folder 29)
- SB 1085 (99) Child Support; Shared Custody (Box 14, Folder 30)
- SB 1089 (99) Commissioners for Promotion of Uniformity of Legislation (Box 14, Folder 31)
- SB 1090 (99) Property Owners' Association Act; Right of Cancellation (Box 14, Folder 32)
- SB 1092 (99) Effect of Entry of Support Order in Garnishment Proceedings (Box 14, Folder 33)
- SB 1095 (99) Authority of Department Directors (Box 14, Folder 34)
- SB 1098 (99) Transient Occupancy Tax (Box 14, Folder 35)
- SB 1102 (99) Insurance; Motor Vehicle Rental Contract Enrollers (Box 14, Folder 36)
- SB 1105 (99) Gas Utilities; Retail Supply Choice (Box 14, Folder 37)
- SB 1106 (99) Field Training Officers; Training Standards (Box 14, Folder 38)
- SB 1107 (99) Law-Enforcement Officers; Certification (Box 14, Folder 39)
- SB 1109 (99) Volunteer Rescue Squads; Participation in Surplus Materials Auctions (Box 14, Folder 40)
- SB 1111 (99) Department of General Services; Disposition of Surplus Materials (Box 14, Folder 41)
- SB 1112 (99) Public Procurement Act; Exemptions for Health Care Services (Box 14, Folder 42)
- SB 1117 (99) Parking Violation Notices (Box 14, Folder 43)
- SB 1119 (99) Commonwealth Transportation Board (CTB) (Box 14, Folder 44)
- SB 1122 (99) Absentee Voting and Applications for Absentee Ballots (Box 14, Folder 45)
- SB 1123 (99) Elections Procedures (Box 14, Folder 46)
- SB 1124 (99) Cancellation of Voter Registration (Box 14, Folder 47)
- SB 1126 (99) School Board Salaries; Hampton (Box 14, Folder 48)
- SB 1127 (99) Small Business Investment Fund (Box 14, Folder 49)
- SB 1128 (99) Intervention Program for Suspended and Expelled Students (Box 14, Folder 50)
- SB 1129 (99) Certified Nurse Aid Programs (Box 14, Folder 51)
- SB 1130 (99) Employment; Critical Shortage of Qualified Workers List (Box 14, Folder 52)
- SB 1131 (99) Health Statistics for Minority Populations (Box 14, Folder 53)
- SB 1134 (99) Personal Property Tax on Certain Small Boats and Watercraft (Box 14, Folder 54)
- SB 1135 (99) Student Expulsions for Drug Offenses (Box 14, Folder 55)
- SB 1136 (99) Student Expulsions (Box 14, Folder 56)
- SB 1138 (99) Property Owners' Association Act; Meetings of Board of Directors (Box 14, Folder 57)
- SB 1139 (99) Public Procurement Act; Community Reinvestment Activities (Box 14, Folder 59)
- SB 1142 (99) Tourism Authority Act; Created (Box 14, Folder 59)
- SB 1143 (99) Investment Partnership Act; Created (Box 14, Folder 60)
- SB 1144 (99) Tolls for Motorcycles (Box 14, Folder 61)
- SB 1145 (99) Education Accountability and Quality Enhancement Act of 1999 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- SB 1146 (99) Small Business Environmental Compliance Assistance Fund (Box 14, Folder 63)
- SB 1147 (99) Virginia Water Facilities Revolving Load Fund (Box 14, Folder 64)
- SB 1148 (99) Homestead Exceptions; Retirement Benefit Exemptions (Box 14, Folder 65)
- SB 1149 (99) Appointment of Members of a Governing Body (Box 14, Folder 66)
- SB 1153 (99) Neighborhood Assistance Act; Donation of Professional Services (Box 14, Folder 67)
- SB 1154 (99) Health Professions; Pharmacy (Box 14, Folder 68)
- SB 1158 (99) Patient Records (Box 14, Folder 69)
- SB 1159 (99) Payment of Medical Fees; Criminal Cases (Box 14, Folder 70)
- SB 1160 (99) Virginia Taxable Income; Subtraction for Military Basic Pay (Box 14, Folder 71)
- SB 1165 (99) Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission and Fund (Box 14, Folder 72)
- SB 1166 (99) Assault and Battery Against a Family Member (Box 14, Folder 73)
- SB 1168 (99) Board of Social Services; Employment Standards (Box 14, Folder 74)
- SB 1171 (99) Post-Secondary Education; Multi-State Compacts (Box 14, Folder 75)
- SB 1172 (99) Nursing Homes (Box 14, Folder 76)
- SB 1173 (99) Adult Care Residences (Box 14, Folder 77)
- SB 1174 (99) Health Care Decisions (Box 14, Folder 78)
- SB 1175 (99) Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Barring Invitees of a Tenant (Box 14, Folder 79)
- SB 1176 (99) Health Insurance; Fair Business Practice (Box 14, Folder 80)
- SB 1178 (99) Experimental Family Courts (Box 14, Folder 81)
- SB 1186 (99) Medicaid Provider Communication (Box 14, Folder 82)
- SB 1187 (99) Enterprise Zone Designation (Box 14, Folder 83)
- SB 1188 (99) Information Technology Employment Performance Grant Program (Box 14, Folder 84)
- SB 1190 (99) Temporary Assistance to Needy Families (TANF) Program (Box 14, Folder 85)
- SB 1191 (99) Board of Medicine; Athletic Trainer Certification (Box 14)
- SB 1193 (99) Antique Motor Vehicles; Registration (Box 14, Folder 87)
- SB 1194 (99) Limited Liability Companies; Contributions to Members (Box 14, Folder 88)
- SB 1196 (99) Early Intervention Services Systems (Box 14, Folder 89)
- SB 1198 (99) Location of Highway Routes (Box 14, Folder 90)
- SB 1199 (99) School Division Participation in Medical Assistance Services (Box 14, Folder 91)
- SB 1200 (99) Virginia Gifted Education Consortium (Box 14, Folder 92)
- SB 1201 (99) Caps on Landfill Disposal (Box 15, Folder 1)
- SB 1202 (99) Water and Waste Authorities Act; Exemption From Utilities Facilities Act (Box 15, Folder 2)
- SB 1203 (99) Virginia Airports Revolving Fund (Box 15, Folder 3)
- SB 1210 (99) Clinch Valley College (Box 15, Folder 4)
- SB 1214 (99) Health; Telemedicine (Box 15, Folder 5)
- SB 1216 (99) Release of Information on Juvenile Criminal Charges (Box 15, Folder 6)
- SB 1217 (99) Health Insurance; Small Employer Market Provisions (Box 15, Folder 7)
- SB 1218 (99) Tax Credits; Preservation of Land (Box 12, Folder 8)
- SB 1219 (99) Public Recreational Facilities Authorities (Box 15, Folder 9)
- SB 1220 (99) Personal Representatives and Trustees (Box 15, Folder 10)
- SB 1221 (99) Tax Increment Financing; Open-Space Uses (Box 15, Folder 11)
- SB 1222 (99) Capital Gains Tax; Relief for Land Dedicated to Open Space (Box 15, Folder 12)
- SB 1224 (99) Mental Retardation, Developmental Disabilities, or Mental Illness (Box 15, Folder 13)
- SB 1229 (99) ABC; Regulations of the ABC Board (Box 15, Folder 14)
- SB 1230 (99) Medical Malpractice Limits (Box 15, Folder 15)
- SB 1231 (99) Riverside Regional Jail Authority (Box 15, Folder 16)
- SB 1233 (99) Charitable Gaming (Box 15, Folder 17)
- SB 1234 (99) Charitable Gaming; Permits (Box 15, Folder 18)
- SB 1235 (99) Licensure of Individuals Conducting Utilization Review (Box 15, Folder 19)
- SB 1237 (99) School Board Salaries (Box 15, Folder 20)
- SB 1241 (99) Comprehensive Services; Membership Requirements (Box 15, Folder 21)
- SB 1242 (99) Housing, Spot Blight Abatement (Box 15, Folder 22)
- SB 1243 (99) Real Estate Appraiser Board; Membership (Box 15, Folder 23)
- SB 1244 (99) Reporting of Student Offenses to School Authorities (Box 15, Folder 24)
- SB 1247 (99) Governor's Economic Development Fund (Box 15, Folder 25)
- SB 1248 (99) Workers' Compensation; Death or Disability, Cancer (Box 15, Folder 26)
- SB 1250 (99) Suicide Prevention in Public Schools (Box 15, Folder 27)
- SB 1254 (99) Liens for Water and Sewer Charges (Box 15, Folder 28)
- SB 1256 (99) High Priority Transit Project Fund (Box 15, Folder 29)
- SB 1257 (99) Statewide Workforce Training Council; Membership, Powers (Box 15, Folder 30)
- SB 1258 (99) Board for Contractors; Continuing Education (Box 15, Folder 31)
- SB 1259 (99) Cruelty to Animals (Box 15, Folder 32)